[
    {
        "question": "Are there any good restaurants nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalRestaurant}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I find the best restaurant in the area?",
        "answer": "{LocalRestaurant}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the nearest convenience store?",
        "answer": "{LocalConvenienceStore}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a 24-hour store nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalConvenienceStore}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the nearest bank?",
        "answer": "{LocalBank}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there any ATMs nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalATM}"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nearest hospital?",
        "answer": "{LocalHospital}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a pharmacy nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalPharmacy}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a laundromat nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalLaundromat}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there any recommended places to visit nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalAttraction}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there any tourist places to visit nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalAttraction}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there any poppular places to visit nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalAttraction}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there any souvenir shop nearby?",
        "answer": "{LocalSouvenir}"
    }

    
]
